# TADEVOSIAN Sarkis

Junior Data Scientist



- Pruxelles, BE
- **\** 0498/59.18.67
- ™ tadevosian.sarkis@gmail.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/sarkistadevosian
- https://github.com/Ta-DevSark

## SKILLS

- Programming language: Python, SQL
- Data analysis and visualization: Pandas, NumPy
- Machine learning: Scikit-Learn
- Database Management
- Cloud platforms: AWS (certified cloud practitioner)

# **TOOLS**

- MySQL
- Docker
- Tableau
- MongoDB
- VS Code

# LANGUAGES

- French (native) English (CI)
- Ducth (BI) Armenian (mothertongue)

### **PROFILE**

As I continue to evolve and grow within the data science field, I am excited to leverage my unique blend of experiences to contribute effectively to teams, projects, and initiatives that demand critical thinking, problem-solving, and a data-centric mindset.

## 8

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### BeCode, Junior Data Scientist

04/2023 - present | Bruxelles

BeCode is an intensive 7-month bootcamp using an active pedagogy through a series of projects designed to be completed with a high degree of autonomy, closely simulating real-world professional scenarios.

Main projects realized so far:

- Dragonyte Brewery (Business challenge) Accenture
- Belgian Newspaper Articles Sentiment Analysis on Data Related Topics – Data Tank
- Belgian Parliament semantic search tool Akkanto

#### **ZP MONS-QUEVY,** Inspector of Police

07/2019 - 08/2022 | Mons, Belgium

 Active officer for 3 years in the Intervention Service, also called the Police Rescue Service.

#### Police Academy, Police cadet

06/2018 – 06/2019 | Jurbise, Belgium

· Academic training.

#### La Belge Maison, Intern

10/2017 - 05/2018 | Mons, Belgium

 Internship at a financial institution specializing in real estate and mortgage services, along with insurance offerings.

#### 1

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **UMons University**

2016 | Mons, Belgium

• Completed 3 years of Bachelor in the Law faculty of the university of Mons.

## **CERTIFICATES**

• AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner (CLF)